https://www.towamencinmennonite.org/index.php/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
Home  Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Towamencin Mennonite Church is located at:
1980 Sumneytown Pike Kulpsville,  PA  19443 215-368-2450
It is Towamencin Mennonite Church’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to www.towamencinmennonite.org and vbs.towamencinmennonite.org (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, “towamencinmennonite.org”, or “vbs.towamencinmennonite.org”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Towamencin Mennonite Church collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Towamencin Mennonite Church’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Towamencin Mennonite Church’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Towamencin Mennonite Church may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Towamencin Mennonite Church also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://vbs.towamencinmennonite.org blog posts. Towamencin Mennonite Church only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Towamencin Mennonite Church’s websites choose to interact with Towamencin Mennonite Church in ways that require Towamencin Mennonite Church to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Towamencin Mennonite Church gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://vbs.towamencinmennonite.org to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Aggregated Statistics
Towamencin Mennonite Church may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Towamencin Mennonite Church may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Towamencin Mennonite Church does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Towamencin Mennonite Church uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Towamencin Mennonite Church uses cookies to help Towamencin Mennonite Church identify and track visitors, their usage of https://vbs.towamencinmennonite.org, and their website access preferences. Towamencin Mennonite Church visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Towamencin Mennonite Church’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Towamencin Mennonite Church’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Towamencin Mennonite Church’s use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Towamencin Mennonite Church may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Towamencin Mennonite Church’s sole discretion. Towamencin Mennonite Church encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Credit & Contact Information
This privacy policy was created at termsandconditionstemplate.com. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
Live Stream Only - Sunday 12-06-2020
To our Church Family at Towamencin:
Our leadership team is recommending that we cancel the In-Person services for this coming Sunday, December 6th, due to a number of people in the congregation being exposed to the COVID virus.
The service will still be Live Streamed at the normal service time of 9:00am.  This is not what we want to do, but feel that for the health of the congregation, we need to protect their well-being.  We will re-evaluate at the end of this coming week. Please be in prayer for our church family & spend time in God’s Word
Love you ALL!
The Leadership Team
×
